[
  {
    "product_id": 1,
    "licence_name": "Star Wars",
    "category_name": "Figuras coleccionables",
    "product_name": "Baby Yoda Blueball",
    "product_description": "Figura coleccionable Star Wars",
    "product_price": 1799.99,
    "dues": 10,
    "product_sku": "STW001001",
    "img_front": "/img/star-wars/baby-yoda-1.webp",
    "img_back": "/img/star-wars/baby-yoda-box.webp"
  },
  {
    "product_id": 2,
    "licence_name": "Star Wars",
    "category_name": "Figuras coleccionables",
    "product_name": "Boba Fett Fighter",
    "product_description": "Figura coleccionable Star Wars",
    "product_price": 1799.99,
    "dues": 10,
    "product_sku": "STW001002",
    "img_front": "/img/star-wars/bobbafeth-1.webp",
    "img_back": "/img/star-wars/bobbafeth-box.webp"
  },
  {
    "product_id": 3,
    "licence_name": "Star Wars",
    "category_name": "Figuras coleccionables",
    "product_name": "Luke Skywalker & Grogu",
    "product_description": "Figura coleccionable Star Wars",
    "product_price": 1799.99,
    "dues": 10,
    "product_sku": "STW001003",
    "img_front": "/img/star-wars/luke-1.webp",
    "img_back": "/img/star-wars/luke-box.webp"
  },
  {
    "product_id": 4,
    "licence_name": "Star Wars",
    "category_name": "Figuras coleccionables",
    "product_name": "Stormtrooper Lightsaber",
    "product_description": "Figura coleccionable Star Wars",
    "product_price": 1799.99,
    "dues": 10,
    "product_sku": "STW001004",
    "img_front": "/img/star-wars/trooper-1.webp",
    "img_back": "/img/star-wars/trooper-box.webp"
  },
  {
    "product_id": 5,
    "licence_name": "Pokemon",
    "category_name": "Figuras coleccionables",
    "product_name": "Charmander Smiley",
    "product_description": "Figura coleccionable Pokemon",
    "product_price": 1799.99,
    "dues": 10,
    "product_sku": "PKM001001",
    "img_front": "/img/pokemon/charmander-1.webp",
    "img_back": "/img/pokemon/charmander-box.webp"
  },
  {
    "product_id": 6,
    "licence_name": "Pokemon",
    "category_name": "Figuras coleccionables",
    "product_name": "Dragonite Hi!",
    "product_description": "Figura coleccionable Pokemon",
    "product_price": 1799.99,
    "dues": 10,
    "product_sku": "PKM001002",
    "img_front": "/img/pokemon/dragonite-1.webp",
    "img_back": "/img/pokemon/dragonite-box.webp"
  },
  {
    "product_id": 7,
    "licence_name": "Pokemon",
    "category_name": "Figuras coleccionables",
    "product_name": "Pidgeotto Flying",
    "product_description": "Figura coleccionable Pokemon",
    "product_price": 1799.99,
    "dues": 10,
    "product_sku": "PKM001003",
    "img_front": "/img/pokemon/pidgeotto-1.webp",
    "img_back": "/img/pokemon/pidgeotto-box.webp"
  },
  {
    "product_id": 8,
    "licence_name": "Pokemon",
    "category_name": "Figuras coleccionables",
    "product_name": "Pikachu Smiley",
    "product_description": "Figura coleccionable Pokemon",
    "product_price": 1799.99,
    "dues": 10,
    "product_sku": "PKM001004",
    "img_front": "/img/pokemon/pikachu-1.webp",
    "img_back": "/img/pokemon/pikachu-box.webp"
  },
  {
    "product_id": 9,
    "licence_name": "Pokemon",
    "category_name": "Figuras coleccionables",
    "product_name": "Vulpix Fancy",
    "product_description": "Figura coleccionable Pokemon",
    "product_price": 1799.99,
    "dues": 10,
    "product_sku": "PKM001005",
    "img_front": "/img/pokemon/vulpix-1.webp",
    "img_back": "/img/pokemon/vulpix-box.webp"
  },
  {
    "product_id": 10,
    "licence_name": "Harry Potter",
    "category_name": "Figuras coleccionables",
    "product_name": "Harry Potter & Hegwid",
    "product_description": "Figura coleccionable Harry Potter",
    "product_price": 1799.99,
    "dues": 10,
    "product_sku": "HT001001",
    "img_front": "/img/harry-potter/harry-1.webp",
    "img_back": "/img/harry-potter/harry-box.webp"
  },
  {
    "product_id": 11,
    "licence_name": "Harry Potter",
    "category_name": "Figuras coleccionables",
    "product_name": "Hermione Ball Dress",
    "product_description": "Figura coleccionable Harry Potter",
    "product_price": 1799.99,
    "dues": 10,
    "product_sku": "HT001002",
    "img_front": "/img/harry-potter/hermione-1.webp",
    "img_back": "/img/harry-potter/hermione-box.webp"
  },
  {
    "product_id": 12,
    "licence_name": "Harry Potter",
    "category_name": "Figuras coleccionables",
    "product_name": "Luna Lovegood Lion Mask",
    "product_description": "Figura coleccionable Harry Potter",
    "product_price": 1799.99,
    "dues": 10,
    "product_sku": "HT001003",
    "img_front": "/img/harry-potter/luna-1.webp",
    "img_back": "/img/harry-potter/luna-box.webp"
  },
  {
    "product_id": 13,
    "licence_name": "Harry Potter",
    "category_name": "Figuras coleccionables",
    "product_name": "Snape Patronus",
    "product_description": "Figura coleccionable Harry Potter",
    "product_price": 1799.99,
    "dues": 10,
    "product_sku": "HTM001004",
    "img_front": "/img/harry-potter/snape-patronus-1.webp",
    "img_back": "/img/harry-potter/snape-patronus-box.webp"
  }
]
